I put a spell
Untrue
Get the fuck up here. What are you guys doing?
Come on
If it's a link up, I didn't feel like I'm so sorry. Hi guys
Hi
Licks up up
People are like this old weird
It's like
Do you want me do a song? I mean, it's like that. I did not happen with anything
Hi guys.
Here, there I am.
Oh my gosh, my off-camera.
Hi, oh.
Okay, let's fix this.
See, I love the green screen, see how cool it is?
I can basically have any poster I want on it.
So I can say like, okay, what's my mood today?
What kind of poster do I want?
Because we always have a different poster we want, right?
I can say, okay, well today I want
an interesting poster. Let me see. Oh, this one. This looks pretty good. Let's see.
There. What do you guys think of this? I can even put it in my full background too.
Watch this. Oh, there we go. I mean, it kind of looks like me a little bit. What's that?
Pretty pretty pretty cool
I
Thought I come on one more time every all the plans fell through. I have one more drink. I
Need you guys help I need to like you guys to spread the word about this channel because this is a new channel
You didn't know
You know you too, but I
Had a little hissy fit about my content and believe my channel, but you know what?
I'm back. I'm back, baby, better than ever, right?
Bitter than ever. Oh my gosh. So what I got today. They're so good.
That's why they have these cookies.
It's oatmeal raisins. How good is that? They're good cookies.
So I not like to say literally
It's at the time they could see if they could see if they look at me. I
Didn't my sandwich there was a special at some way up everyone looked at me. Oh my gosh
Well, hey tricks you're gonna come up here at tricks. I need some like I need some uh
Some cat power that cat power for me. I see that can I see you? Oh, you're cutie. Oh
Hi, babe
Hi everyone says oh you grab your cats by the neck
I don't I grab them by the under them and then I hit their neck very gently
And so that's what they like
They get I know you don't okay
Trick number a year ago
You almost under my neighbors
They had you for a couple days, and I was missing you so bad and I was so sad I was almost crying
I was like how could I let tricks and then they brought you back, and they said they're allergic, right?
To your mind forever, okay
He's a great cat you're a great cat, huh?
You're a little girl baby, huh? You're a little baby this morning. I woke up and he was like
Going nuts until I got put him under the blanket with me and hugged him. He just needs to hug sometimes
So do I I need a hug sometimes
Yeah, go ahead and say hi in the chat guys unless you're like some kind of like evil troll or something
I do want to say hi to people. I don't want to like sit here alone. I'm like some chute
I don't know. It's kind of funny funny word chute
sounds like
Cucaracha or something
Okay, well
No one's in it comes all play more music and then I'll leave if nobody comes
If people don't like the music, I mean, it's like not bad music. It's like
Pretty good
I'm not biased, but I am biased.
The next day she was like it wasn't about you you fucking moron like that basically like that
Like that. I said why even think it was so you said it was and then I was like, oh my gosh. She's nuts. Oh
Oh, who do we have here?
Who's this? Who's this guy? Oh?
What's that?
Yes, what is that?
You're a math. Oh my god
Your true self
Oh
Can you suck it up again one
the
it looks like you're wearing a green fizz
it looks like, uh, I can't see your face or what you're wearing
so it looks like
it doesn't matter what you're wearing about it
hmm
and Gaudi, what are you wearing?
Gaudi's wearing like a
is it like a bag full of candy?
Gaudi, it looks like
it looks like actually
excuse me, God
it looks like
the
I'm gonna do a hell I'm gonna do black magic. I want to see it. I want to see his dick disappear inside of
So I keep taking his entire wall in green
and this still is all fucked up
W
I don't mind you didn't know, I'm so sorry
oh yeah, you said sorry lately
I'm sorry, I don't mean to interrupt
like I see you guys, I'm sorry
you do too
now I know
now I know why 300 glow got stabbed
W
yeah, I got stabbed right here
Know why this nigga got stabbed in the chest now. I know why your heart is like a little over to the left
Oh, but you that's why now. I know why
is that in the center of it? Oh, I'm sorry. I'm gonna stab somebody, stab them in the heart.
I'm gonna beat that one out.
That's what you do, motherfucker, and you gotta make sure that the blade is more than three inches.
Yeah, what the fuck?
In New York City, in New York City, what they say is the blade doesn't, if the New York City,
the blade doesn't penetrate more than two, or I think maybe even three inches into the body.
it does not count as an attempt at murder, it's just in the soul
that is what she said, yeah sure that's what she said
but that's the law
you stab someone even if the blade enters their chest
like literally it's in their chest cavity
if the blade did not enter into their chest cavity 3 inches
it does not count as attempted murder, that's how it is
okay
I disagree with it
I'm wearing a signal costume, do I look like
you live in California
You know, yeah, you look like a fucking bitch with all the Hot Wheels cars around you nigga. Yeah, you look like a bitch
Well, I look like signal I got a bunch of Halloween card hot Hot Wheels cars around
Shit worth more money
I have one motorcycle that's more worth more than all your hot wheels nigger put CSN
Your motorcycle in a hot wheel that's worth more than your
Stupid
I think he's the real JD. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not
Oh my god
You ain't gonna like those signals dick when you suck in it, so he goes laughs
I don't want to swear and glow like this. I just want to like
Arms what does it call the Los Monos? Yes? Yes
Here's mono. Hey, I'm really from Jalisco, Guadalajara
Jalisco, Guadalajara, Mexico. I'm from
Santa Muerte
That's what we believe in Santa Muerte
You are hey stop saying that name
a
Negative energy talking on the the devil on like the
As bad as Santa muerte coming for you
You can think of other things that are bad luck
in my pocket
yeah
congratulations buddy
typical
Funtime point by English
GD is phantasma
See hey, you know where all the white boys from while I come from from me. Yeah, I'm that bloodline
phantasma
because you'll JD and I are I think by
Hey psyche I didn't look wider than you nigga
It's white people I think white people are too dark. They're like the devil why people are too pink
We are too pink
I don't know pink in the white people have high blood pressure
thanks to your ancestors drinking vodka and sandray and moonshine
yeah well it's just called tolizania i will blush
white hey you remember uh we're seeing that mcdonald's movie the big size where he
where the white boy eats 10 mcdonald's merc
fucking big max what what do you think yes i love pressure
The devil and I'm over here by a corner tacos nothing but a real fool
Tacos every day
In the jungle they look healthy
I went I've been a part of iarta and they take you into the jungle is literally a jungle and there's people living there
You're like what the fuck is going on?
America why you guys all sitting down you guys been sitting down all day already why you guys sit down for
I want you guys want to check out
Yeah I did
Why does everyone sit down?
Y'all sit down around all day for hours
Bro your backs are gonna blow out
Y'all gonna stand up for a little bit
Your back gonna blow out
I like you to stand up
Cause I can see your butt and then
I'm happy old man
Yeah that's what you like for show Psyche
I'mma show you
That's part of this. Hey, psyche, send me send me 100 and I got you. You've been to Africa. You've
been to Africa. Have you ever been to Africa? Well, it has to be personal. You can upload it. Have you
ever been to Africa dog? Have you ever been to Africa? Why the fuck would I go to Africa if I'm
Mexican? Have you ever been to Africa? I'm Mexican. So what? What do you mean so what?
My ancestors in Mexican and Aracha, why would I go to Africa? That's not my that's not where my generation is from
jungle in Mexico
What do you mean?
What kind of public?
Let's see.
You know.
This thing has his camera off.
Kick him out.
You know there's a camera.
Hey, I'm a public figure that's not public.
You're not a public figure.
I can't be showing much.
You're not.
I forgot.
You're a racist.
You're a racist public figure.
You listen here.
You're a racist mother of an asshole.
where the point is
I'm gonna put 300 below next to me
I'll put JD next to God
hey thank y'all some real shit
we could have fun you know what's up
we could like do some
nozz
pasta
we could have fun right
have fun stop being weird
I'm not gonna torture you and shit
I'm not gonna fucking like
it's getting you or something like some weird shit
So you're more related to what's that niggas name the name the pervert that gay pervert
He's a peck of it from the valley
Epstein stop it. Yeah, you're related. I'm not even Jewish stop it. You're related. I'm not related to Jeffrey Epps. That's your cousin
That's like your twin brother you didn't like well, I mean I wish it was like an island to visit
I mean, I wish I was his twin brother cuz I would have socked him out whenever I find out and doing that shit
I ought to put them on game
Bitch don't be doing that shit of people
I'm not doing anything
Boy have people around here and then it put it then they didn't check them what I want to know is
Person checking on or a brother that would check them the brother will really check them none of that would have never happened
Damn
Why why Jeffrey Dahmer was walking around all freely doing that shit
Telling them a make a you better act right
I'm coach every dog. Will you? It's just real. It's just real life. Why wasn't there nobody checking it?
What do you say? He had family. He had rich, rich family people. Why was there nobody telling him you're being stupid, bro?
what the fuck
they are just wouldn't listen or something right
what do you say
I don't know
he was in drugs he ran away he bought a
he bought a
apartment
where a signal lives
in the same building where jeffrey
donmer had the apartment
you fucking lying
just don't name your child jeffrey i think jeffrey
you lying
that's where it's saying no let's live that
that's saying no
it's saying he related to who?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah
You want to kill me I'm a screamer card you say that shit again
I'm gonna kill this guy. I'm gonna kill me. I'll be
now
I bet you can't even kill me
You won't be able to kill me cuz you know what cuz I'm fucking your mom bitch
God me your mom are best friends
What I don't I don't believe
he's back, they're hood only, he's back
are you from the mother man?
I'm a brother
I ejaculated inside of your mother
are you from the mother?
W
oh my god
yo I ejaculated inside of your mother
and she loves me for it
what do you do about it?
oh my god
please
Oh my god, I see you want to be like that. Just call me. I'll show you call me
Why do you have tattoos on your hands?
You know why because I don't want to be a veteran. Oh, I'm gonna go get the benefits
Army
You niggas collect ebt like a regular ebt
And it's gonna give me all the benefits
it does
just the last picture on your phone
they get all the benefits more
Well, this is a reflection. Why are you all delusional about that?
He's fine. He smells like he's high.
He's delusional.
Well, there's people that joined the army or the LAPD or whatever cop they are for the benefits.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Fuck yeah, we don't love it anymore.
Hello? Hello?
Hello, bitch.
Hold on.
Hey, giga, he can't hear us.
Well, let me get JD. He can't hear us.
I can hear you. I can hear you.
I can hear you. I can hear you. I can hear you.
Can't I wasn't paying attention to you idiot swat? Who you bitch is a shit?
Bitches you're a bitch. That's who you are
I'm gonna show you what's up
Where are you? Where are you?
I'm in Cali. I'm in South Central.
Where? Where? Where?
Come here and let's show you who you are.
Where?
Where are you at?
Hey, kick this thing out.
This ain't got a wearing mask.
Where you at, bitch?
I'm in South Central.
Where, motherfucker? Where?
South Central. Burning in Central.
Burning in Central.
Hello tomorrow four o'clock
If you ever pull up outside my house, I'ma give you like hello shots
Central Vernon and Central right to down. Yeah, right that shit down nigga
Then again has a mask on cuz he's scared and she
i'll be wearing it when i come see you yeah and then i'm gonna fuck your face
yeah i'm gonna watch it oh my gosh can i make a porno from this i would like to watch it
yes i you got the motion i'll fuck with you nigga
You're not scared nigga. You're like this thing is our bitch is which we don't like
Who the fuck is JD?
Who JD?
These niggas are all retarded on the internet.
Who the fuck is this guy?
You're all retarded on the internet.
Who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck am I?
I'm your daddy, nigga.
Who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck is JD?
You know are you trying to apologize?
You're separate isn't that gross you okay say you're gonna hurt yourself. Well, who even is that?
I
She said
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why
Hey, I just wanted to make it to your glow here. You and me. Oh my God
Yes, what's up, what's up, dude? What's a homie? Hey, uh,
Kitchido, what's that? How do you say? I don't know. Chido. What's up? What's up?
I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to, I want to be the, I want to be the lucky, I want to be the lucky Pedro.
And the second one.
I will, but he's so annoying, he's the same.
Yeah.
So much.
I love you.
you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you
Whoever's out the person is that from some lame as fuck. Whoever that other person
Who is that
I
Are you having like a family gathering there?
He's trying to pretend like someone else. It's me
That's what he diamonds
Hello, that's me 300 dinner. They're in a demon. Is that your wife your wife's a demon?
No
You want to be a demon? You know what?
Ideas Neil, you know, I'm cool. Oh, this let me like
Hand with your husband for a couple hours. You can even like a super guy. I won't touch him. I love you
Yeah, we'll see you
Yes, I seen you
This is his wife his wife is talking. Oh, that's his wife. Oh cool
Why they call themselves 300 though they were like 300 pounds, you know, they're 150 pounds each and so
They're really nice people, they are, they're living in Los Angeles, they're very nice
Latinos.
They're nice people, man.
He's very cute.
We need nice people like this in this country.
I'm not going to say anything.
Don't say anything, JD.
How about roses from him from the side?
Does this have been sweet?
Why is this motherfucker got a pentagram?
It's in front of me.
That's love.
Why you got a pentagram, dude?
You're a slave to the money that you die are you doing black magic on me you're
doing black magic on me you're doing black magic on me you're doing black magic on me
you're doing black magic on me you're doing black magic on me you're doing black magic
Hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate, hecate
You did?
Well, I think we lost our Mexican friends.
I think Mexico has abandoned us.
What's going on?
We have a war against Canada.
And the United States and Mexico.
Are the Mexicans going to be drinking surveys, smoking
motah, and abandoning the white people?
Oh, yeah.
They would abandon us in a heartbeat.
Oh, usually.
My god.
I mean, it's like.
know like where I live it was once Mexico it really was I mean it was
Mexico before yep this was all Mexico all of California all California it's
California I mean it's but it is kind of like a interesting like for occasion or
is it like Johnny is Johnny here what's up Joni
Joni is in Chattanooga
Say you're back on the show. Are you fell asleep already? Oh my god. Yeah, fuck up. He is
You see I saw you on Alexander you went to Alexander's that night after I
Hear a cat. Who's cat at that?
Yeah, cat my stomach. Oh my god
We need an all day. You haven't eaten. Oh my god
What is that noise there's only an animal is in distress
Okay
It's puppy, okay
I read the weirdest story today because I was thinking about like these hoaxes that everyone believed okay
So in like the 1800s or something like a guy in a wheelchair for seven years. Yeah, well, that's just you know
But the story was this woman started like she said she was like pregnant and miscarried or something
But after she saw a rabbit and then she was obsessed with rabbits and stuff
And then she started giving birth to like animal parts like parts of rabbits and like
What the fuck are you talking about?
This is a true story.
This is in England, and then they had like the king,
like the king, I forgot the king's name,
but he was really interested.
They sent all these like doctors and stuff,
and the doctors were like, yeah, she's delivering animal parts.
And there's, I mean, it's like normal.
It's like, I guess they thought it almost like a
Kabbalistic kind of thing.
Kabbalah will say, whoever you're like looking at,
when you like orgasm or something like that,
is like what the child will look like.
I
Yo, thank you. Can I ask psyche? Yes. Why why is it that I mean not every gay man
Because I can say in my experience I've met a lot of gay men that
There is not like a flying point gay sort of thing. It's just like them being gay is a secondary thing
But why is it that there are so many men that they make?
No, it's not about them being gay. They make their promiscuity
Right make the promiscuity of their homosexuality. They make it this sort of like entire element of their
Personality, why is that? Well, aren't there guys that do that when they sit with a lot of women too?
I mean, it's like yeah, but like there's actually you know an old fairness look in all fairness
To address what you're saying in all fairness like
There is kind of like a net result out of that.
Like it's going somewhere, right?
I mean, if some guy is like, if some guy is like, oh, I'm going to fuck this bitch.
I'm going to fuck the shit out of her.
You know, if it goes in the right direction at some point, they're going
to get he's going to get her pregnant.
They're going to have a kid.
They're going to have a family.
But like, where is that direction for gay dude?
That's
We all to say we're like gay people are like a minority in this world, okay?
Why are you speaking for them all you're speaking for all gays?
But let me just say okay, so yes, I disagree with them promiscuity in the gay community, but it is like understandable
I mean, it's like man. Oh you
If a man like goes to another man and they're both it's both sexually ready and stuff like that
Woman it's like oh buy me dinner buy me dinner like it's a you know a few three dates and like you know
And then take your time and then maybe maybe maybe you'll get lucky, but it's a guy. It's like, okay. Yes. Yes
Okay, let's all go right
Bitches are horse
Okay, that's exactly what a gay guy would think all you think you think you're gay, dude
And you think these bitches all the respect you think they're not whoring themselves out you think they're not fucking on the first day
Not everybody the majority are I would say
Here's the thing psyche if you are living in any major city in the fucking earth
If you are living in any major city on earth
Think you can make a pretty fair and reasonable assumption to say yes, that's what every bitch is doing
Sorry, I know I'm bursting a lot of bubbles. It's facts. No, there are
Women there are women that I bless them. God bless them. You know what I mean? I
Won't shout out to all my women that are out there horn themselves out. God bless you
I hope you're happy with your decisions. God bless you
That's not what I'm saying I actually explicitly
Disagreed with that. I actually if you had heard what I said, I actually
Explicitly did say the opposite of what you're saying. Okay, so all right, you know that being said you're not leaving listening to what I'm saying
You're telling me what I just said and then you're incorrect
Okay, you're incorrect. You're saying you're telling me what I just said. You didn't hear me
What more can I say for you my friend?
But you're not listening to what I'm saying
You are not listening to what I'm saying. That's a problem
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I
Okay, well, yeah, that's that's magic in a certain way
But it's like see I that's why I'm not promiscuous because I think sex is a very magical thing
And it can like manifest a lot of things whether it's men and men women and with men or I think it's most powerful
Men and women at manifesting but hey, we have a guest here tonight. Let's welcome to our show
Who said the owl who said the owl?
Jonesy Jones wait a minute. I got to tell you something right now. I got to tell you something for us
Wait a minute. I got the same problem. I got the same problem. I have the iPad and the TV
So I don't want all this psyche. What are you trying to do? Are you trying to kill me?
Yes, obviously, he's trying to kill me. If you know what I mean, we won't go there sir. I'm not
Ma'am ma'am, I got a bone to pick ma'am ma'am ma'am. Can you pull over pull?
Do you want to panel the other day talking shit about me?
I've never been on beat us panel. Why was there a troll of me there? I look like you some guy with a mustache
I've never been on beat I don't even think I've hardly been to our place. All right, good
I feel better now
Jamie's here. Hey me. Thank God
I need I need another vaginal
Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie
Silence!
Where's your tongue away?
You find your tongue away, sir.
No, make me. Make me.
I'll make you girl
Don't worry about who I am
It's all bad news
Boys, what's up with you, sir? What's up with you butterco?
I
Like don't let me laugh because when you know what happens when I laugh. Yeah
It comes I think I was I think I was approaching
I think I would say
Mr. Brown sir, mr. Brown
Here I'm here to remove you from this platform. Is that a jerry flag these things happen
know I'm so sorry sir I can I can sense the authenticity of your apology it's
very clear all right mm-hmm I know nothing let's try buttercup
Okay, butter, butterly, butterly nipples, what the fuck?
Yeah, he's butter nipples, buttery nipples.
No, you could say, you could refer to me if you would like, you could refer to me as butter cock.
Oh, gross. No, thank you.
Okay, otherwise, you can refer to me as a psyche.
If that's how you feel, then I appreciate your compliments, my friend.
No, I would love to talk to you in seven mouths.
I'm not afraid of the compliments. All right. That being said, that being said, I would much rather
have it be this like southern loving, sort of like, I don't want to, I don't want to say like,
Where's my son? No, I don't mean to say it. Look, look, I'm obviously obviously
Obviously, you're not a southern individual, but I just
I have other adjectives that I could use and I don't
Aim in a different direction
Excuse me. Do you know what an adjective is?
No, I have no clue.
Interjection.
Do you know what a part is?
Okay, let me make it more simple.
Parts of speech.
Do you know what an noun is?
Interjection.
You know what a prefix is
Well, here's a thing generally this isn't something that you think about but
It's not something that you think about but like then again is you don't have to think about it
I find the way of getting my rock song.
Appreciate you for asking, buddy.
And ma'am, here, individual.
Wesley Brown.
If that's your name, Mr. Brown, give me the name.
Let me ask you, you know, I'm willing to give you a good song.
all right let's see the question is no no no ma'am no ma'am no ma'am if you're going to ask
something out of me ma'am i'm going to ask something out of you that's right i'm fixing to
crash out if you're if you're going to ask me for something then it's only fair for me to ask
I was earlier
It has been more than one occasion I've seen on Psyche's panel that's for sure
This I mean I think I sung the classics in Spanish speaking
You're thinking in an entirely different perspective. Dear lord our savior
This woman is the
I'm happy that you're Jewish
You know, it's funny, you know, it's funny when I was
Literally
Well, you finish
I'm glad that you can judge somebody else's appearance. You can say that they're fat, but you're too scared to show your
You're too scared
For whatever reason, I think I know why but for whatever reason you don't want to show your face
Generally speaking these kinds of people right you don't want to show your face, but okay. Oh, you're this guy
God bless you, buddy. I wish you the best
I'm glad that you were able to
Successfully
Your middle school dreams of making the entire cafeteria laugh. I'm so high
I'm glad that you were able to successfully
Have the entire cafeteria laugh at your like shitty
That was shitty even when you're fucking 12 years old
Oh, we got somebody backstage. Oh
Beat Alex
You know, but then I join and there's actually something
I can't take it. I can't take it. I can't take it. Sorry. I mean it's like, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don
All right, thank you for my song and Johnny's song turned out well too.
Play it.
I love it.
Whose song is this?
For everyone.
This is Goddy's song.
Oh yeah.
You gotta make him teach you one thing.
Goddy's song.
Goddy's God.
Great panel.
Best ever.
Absolutely.
Look at that lip!
I'll show you some lips.
Look at those lips.
That guy called you homie.
What happened that Wesley Brown did?
Wesley Brown did?
Did we bury him?
Are there people like this bitch?
There you go.
That's my brain.
I need to take a piss
I'm big
You guys have a place to grind and make you
Where did that come from?
If you're saying I'm sorry.
Okay, so who are we yelling at here?
Okay, well, so Joni and Split Fries, what's going on here?
Hold on.
You have big trouble.
I don't know what she's talking about.
Get him, Joni, get him.
No.
Nothing.
Nothing
Crickets nothing I said nothing split friends give us give a split personality split fries. No, are you bipolar perhaps? Nope?
No, yeah, don't know don't know nothing
It depends what scenario we're talking about. I don't know
Tony you got to be specific
I'm fixing to crash out
She's fixing the crash out
Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are shown. Ghosts are
It's all as important, it's back.
You can get it back to that.
Well, I just want to make,
I think Alexandra already like let everyone know,
but she is planning to sign over IP to wiki.info.
And so I will have another monetized channel
if everything works out, you know?
And so I just want to shout out to a few of Alexandra.
That'd be so, so, so awesome.
And, and uh.
Shout out.
I liked her from day one.
Yeah, yeah, she's really awesome, and also she did a she just subscribe with on to my show, right?
Yeah, and sick was on that show sick. Oh
Say she's sick. She's kind to you. You have to say you're like kind of picking on her and she's really kind to you
I've seen
Say what do you have to say for yourself? I'm embarrassed to hear. Yeah, don't be mad. Don't be mean to her
Alexandra
Taking it all in but response to what do you have to say?
He's muted. He's really nice
I just heard the n-word
I don't know probably sick
Okay, I want to play the jamie's cowboy song because this is my this is a great song
Thanks for never throwing me to the side
I tried to cry loud enough to wake the cold, but the album isn't.
That's not it.
I'm sorry.
I need to get the right stuff.
This is the Jamie's Cowboys.
Oh, I like motorcycles, too.
Oh, yeah, the motorcycles, too?
Yeah, those motorcycles in the video.
Yeah, they're cool.
Is it?
Nope.
I just played.
What is wrong?
No, come on. Maybe next time you can put like a line back or a quarterback in there for Cowboys, huh? One time
Yeah, oh yeah quarterback. I should have asked for that, but not a quarterback
But you know like a wide receiver, you know like on the game day
Nope, it's an exact song. Why do I keep playing these sex games thing?
Thank you
I'm very high. I'm gonna have to put it. I'm gonna have to go from my YouTube channel. I have it on my channel
I'm a little bit high, I'm a little bit drunk, okay?
A little bit of rock and roll, all in one.
Little bit of country, I'm a little bit, okay,
so this is a Jamie's Cowboys song, okay?
I found it, I found it, I found it, I got it.
Oh, you finally got it, wow!
I finally have it, okay, guys.
Well, enjoy the Jamie's Cowboys song, okay?
This is the Jamie's Cowboys music video premiere today.
Here we go.
Yep, yep, see the rinse?
This is my poppy.
Yumi's ghosting Ted again.
Yeah, no, Ted.
Ghosting.
This is very much her.
Fuck this shit
I'm gonna sit in front of a screen and cry
I can't believe it.
You know what I learned tonight guys?
I learned, I learned the vagina is a beautiful thing.
It's like, it's actually, it looks like a,
it looks like a kind of like a conch.
No, it's fucking gross, I'm sorry.
It's not gross, it's beautiful, it looks like a conch.
No, I've been watching straight porn for research purposes.
It's not a beautiful picture.
Yeah, I've been seeing a lot of weird looking ones
that just don't look like they should exist.
I'm sorry, my friend.
There's a few of vaginas that,
I can't you are you calling me a vagina? Um, no
No, the fatty that was on here before yelling with that weird. Oh, yeah, but he's a total vagina
Say your vagina everyone thinks so. Yeah, there he is. Yeah, there he is and Joni left before I could actually
Apologize
Gotty come on
If you're listening, this is an apology from JD, okay?
All right, all right, all right.
Joni.
That was it.
I apologize.
I apologize, Joni, for hooding your feelings, for abruptly hanging up on you and blocking
you and saying that I don't give a shit about your cat.
I was having a bad day and you triggered me somehow. I don't know what the fuck you said
But it made me have a some sort of meltdown and you were blocked until now
I don't know how long it's been. I don't know what happened, but I
Apologize for my psychotic break, Joanie
That's my apology. That's pretty good apology personally, but you know
Yeah, but yeah, we all make mistakes. We all make mistakes and we all get a second chance right psych
I mean I give second third fourth fifth and six chances because yeah, and I just want to apologize
If I ever did anything wrong, and I know you're out there listening whoever. Oh, sorry
a lot of things happen after the wreck and I'm trying to pull myself together and
If I did anything if I didn't do anything, I just want a closure. I just want peace with everything. I don't hate you
I don't hate anybody
That person was very rude to me and said
But you know what
Maybe it was an I was an asshole I've learned you know
I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just like, I'm just
I just want to be a small town boy sounds like Bronzeberg too much. It's like
I'm trying my best. I'm trying my best. So I'm saying you just saying a little bit for us. I'm trying my best
Okay, yeah, it's a straight this one
Sing that one I think I've done that before
Hey, Buenos Diaz
Combatria speedy Gonzales the fastest
I mean here's the thing look psyche if you want like if you're thinking like romantic Spanish speaking music, okay
I could do better. I could do better than that. Yes. I mean there's better
Wait, no this song right here. It's the one that's like
Turn away, turn away, turn away, turn away, no, that's not romantic to me.
Turn away, turn away, turn away, run away, run away, run away, that's not okay.
Yeah, how about this song? Kick you off the show because you're being annoying.
How about that song? Let's see. Let's remember that song.
That song is really good. I remember I was taking my ex-girlfriend.
Across the Queensboro Bridge
There's a cross of this is the Queensboro Bridge. She lived in Queens and I was walking in my hand and her parents
Her parents kicked us out
You know, I thought we're gonna sleep at her place. I thought we're gonna sleep at her place and
Then we got there and it's Christmas, right? And they're like, oh no get the fuck out of here
And so we had we spent the whole night out
We walked across the Queensboro Bridge and we walked behind and everything, we spent the night out.
It was cool, there was people that were also out at night, you know, just celebrating, it was chill as fuck.
I remember I like, I was like, I don't know, 17 or something, 16?
And I was like asking random people on the street for cigarettes, because I mean, I couldn't buy a cigarette, it's 21.
That show is funny. I was in and I was blasting this music. I was on the Queensboro
I was blasting the news outside for yeah
What's the point of the story there's no point man, you just live your life
Sike, what's the point to your story? There is no point. You just
Inspiration man, you're just living your life psyche, right?
Well, yeah, I mean that's like the very basic I'm not disagreeing with that I'm just saying like
That's a basic. Yeah, obviously you could be dead, but you're not
We're all survivors you're here you woke up the next day congratulations
Congratulations, you woke up the next day. I'm happy for you. No, well, I don't know if you're gonna wake up tomorrow
See, that's what I'm worried about right now. It's like you're drinking though. You could be a half the next day is not promised
That's the fact
that's that goes without saying psyche come on
but you know what if it's not promised does that mean our life is over does that mean that life
it doesn't mean that it's over but it just means it's not promise that's it no there's no further
there's no further analysis needed it's just
No, just know that tomorrow is not promised. That's it act accordingly
Tomorrow is not promised act accordingly. That's it
Behave accordingly and I'm saying that to everybody in chat. I'm saying it to this bitch here that has an attitude
The tomorrow is not guaranteed behave accordingly
Behave accordingly worry about the people that you actually love in your life. That's all I got to say my girl
Have a good one. I love you. God bless you and I hope all good for you, but you know
I'm hoping good for you and that's why I'm saying what I'm saying
Okay tomorrow is unpromised worry about the people that you really love all I got to say
All I got to say my girl
Cheers
It's math, I'm smoking math, so what
Bottled math, right so what?
So that's still a double you still double you
You're doing are you doing gay sex now?
Drinking bottle meth isn't a double you
The next thing that people do with the bottle you're gonna are you gonna tell me yeah, wait, we'll hold on psyche
Can I ask you real quick psyche?
What do you think about David Bowie?
by sexual he's actually a Capricorn. No, I'm not asking you if he's gay or not
I'm just like what is your opinion of him as a person?
I like him because he was a labyrinth, and I saw him do the labyrinth.
Oh, you love labyrinth. Yeah, he was brilliant in that, so.
What do you mean labyrinth? Is that an, is that an astrological sign?
A movie called Labyrinth.
Labyrinth is a movie with Denver, Connolly, and David Bowie from the 80s,
and it was one of the first movies I ever saw.
It's an 80s movie? I've never seen it, okay.
Jim Hanson is a puppeterian, Jim Hanson.
Listen, whore, excuse me, excuse me, psyche.
Excuse me, psyche. Excuse me, whore. I didn't ask you. I'll do respect.
You know what I mean? What you gave, psyche, excuse me. I don't mean to be rude.
I don't mean to be rude, but what you give is what you get, all right?
This bitch wants to be talking shit to me, so you know what I mean?
But psyche, psyche, I'm being respectful to you. You know what I mean?
We're having this conversation. All right.
I'm having this conversation with you. This, you know, or
What's to be like talking like what's up now? You want to know?
What I mean to say is now this person wants to be all respectful and sir, right? I was talking earlier
Okay, let's have a conversation. Let's this and that right and so now now that we're having a conversation
That's pertinent and we're going to more of the conversation. That's your honor. That's a problem. Anyways
Okay, hey was psyche. Let's take yo psyche. Are you what are you drinking on or what are you doing?
Let's let's take it look, I'm done too. Let's go
Fuck that stupid whore fuck that stupid heart. I'm bitch. We'll see all blown out of shit
But say so look into like 1984 or 1985 there's a movie called labyrinth. That's the best movies I think in that period
Yeah
It's because like like the technology was getting better
Like everything was getting cheaper and better and like it's not just gonna better. Yeah
It was puppets in that movie it was you know, basically puppets. Oh, thank you, JD for being on the show by the way
Thank you, JD. You're awesome
Yeah, it's a piece puppets and labyrinth, but David Bowie plays this like the goblin king and he kidnapped
Kidnapped Jennifer Connelly's like little like Davey brother and then she goes to just go to this labyrinth to like find
Them and stuff right and she makes all these trolls and like these weird like all these weird and elaborate
There's almost a possible and it's all weird and and then David Bowie's like kind of in love with her
Did you ever see did you ever see pans labyrinth? Yes? Oh, that's great, too. Yes. Oh my god. That's the movie
I saw that movie and I was like what the fuck
But it's really good. It's actually the first time I saw it
I was just like what the fuck?
It's kind of a horror movie
But it's it's more than a horror movie. Yeah, you watch it again. It's a little bit more in the horror movie
Do you recommend people watch that it's up? I think it's like Guillermo del Toro. He's a yeah from Spain exactly
Yeah, he's a very interest. He's like really it's an interesting like grotesque kind of like weird
Artistic form, but that is a great movie. It's about this like it can take place in a more modern day
But this girl that like moves to Spain and like the when it's a fascist kind of dictatorship
And her mom is pregnant and falls in love with his high-ranking general
And he's like this asshole really abusive and stuff
But he's all his power and stuff and then she like goes to this labyrinth that's old ruin and she's she meets the god pan
He's always giving her tasks and stuff and she's having this whole kind of Alice in Wonderland like fantasy experience
during this whole wartime
with all these crazy things are happening. It's really interesting because the pan is elaborate. I'm not going to give too much away of the movie, but it's very good.
The movie came out in like 2010.
Yeah.
Yeah. You don't have to go out and see it.
I can't describe it like well, but if you see it, you're really like, wow, there's, and it's like, especially if you're like...
before your spiritual awakening.
I think everyone has a spiritual awakening basically.
But that movie will like help it along in a little bit.
And I think that's what Sticks kind of saying is like,
is like, what is this movie about?
Like what is this?
And it's like, it hits so many parts of like
our like our actual soul feelings.
And I don't know, it is, it's a really good movie.
You just check it out guys.
It looks like you know, and this is a new channel and stuff and I know there's not that many people coming tonight
I don't know why it was kind of like but the panel is on fire. I think the panel is a great panel tonight
I finished my gear
I'm out of pot. I have one oatmeal raisin cookie. I have like few hits of tobacco left
Well, here's the thing psyche. There's number gonna be a shortage of people trying to
You know whispering your ear and tell you what you need to believe. There's never gonna be a shortage of those
The question is if that's your fun if you think that that's fun, then I guess it's not a problem
If what is fun just whispering someone's ear and putting ideas in their head or what excuse me?
Let me just I'm gonna sneeze real quick. Okay
Yeah, I'm true
Actually, I actually need I actually still need this needs but this needs one way. Anyways
Anyways, yeah, my point is
Um, I mean, I'm I yeah, my point is I'm not saying anything. You're not aware of
You're not stupid
Right, but it's like also what you're saying could be like
to interpret it like a thousand different ways, right, and so it's...
How? I mean, really? Could it be? How?
It could, because it's like, what are you talking about exactly? Like, what do you know? Like, where are you coming from? Are you psychic? Are you...
Well, I'm not psychic. I'm just telling you, like, basic...
Basic reasoning would indicate, you know, be careful.
You're like, you don't need to be a psychic.
are you warning me is that a warning to me or is that a warning to everybody or like tell me like what what do you say me be careful
I mean you can make a warning specifically to someone but like you can also make a general warning
Make what specifically to me tell me something not I'm not making it. I'm not making any sort of like specific warning
I'm just saying like be careful. Well, everyone you know take care of yourself, right?
Watch your step. That's another way to say it or it's not it's not even just watch your step. It's like, you know, like I'm I like I'm looking at people
like I look over to my right. I look over my left. You know what I mean? And nobody has their fucking seatbelts on.
Right, this is like this is sort of basic shit. Excuse me. No disrespect man, but I didn't I really didn't fucking ask you
No disrespect
No disrespect, but thank you for your input. I appreciate your input, but I really didn't ask for it that being said
You know, I mean
You know, I'm not I'm not disagreeing psyche with what you're saying. Okay
There's a lot of input to be given people will listen
Right. This is how it is. You just gotta take care of yourself, bro. You just gotta take care of yourself.
Yo, Psyche, Psyche, you gotta get, you gotta get a headstone like that.
You gotta get like a giant fucking statue where it's Psyche and every, all that shit. You gotta do that.
I mean, maybe I will. Not when I die, though, because-
You should do that. No, no, no, no, no. Don't wait until you're dead. It's too late.
Psyche, now.
Yeah, don't wait until you're dead. Come on. My family doesn't have we don't do funerals. We do like
Like we don't we don't want to do with the concrete whatever, you know, you gotta get a meter of marble or some shit
Yeah, I want to you can you do it because you know, I really do want it to be made by do it
I can't guarantee I can't guarantee you that you're gonna look like the fucking Roman
Statues are I can't guarantee that for you, but like I'll give you a good shot
I will do I will do you right? You know what I mean? I'm gonna do my best. I mean I'll do my best
I'm there. I'm no fucking Roman, you know, honestly, you look at the Roman statues. It's like
It's so perfect. Like really like
Maybe it was just the aliens. Maybe it was just the fucking aliens
I saw what I saw roman statues. It looks just like m&m. Have you seen that statue? I'm sick. I haven't seen that
but I mean my point is
You look at the roman statues. Is it really a human made creation or is that just the fucking aliens?
Well, I think it's alien. I'll tell you why because this exists in the world
Okay, I'm gonna show you a picture right now. So this picture is just too perfect
It's too perfect. So is this is this this is really a Roman emperor. Just tell me is it was a Roman emperor?
or are like some M&M fans having fun with me?
I just-
There's just one of the different emperors in different like sort of leaders in the ancient
worlds.
But this is like supposedly, this is like a museum, this is like a supposed statue of
a Roman emperor.
Is this real?
Okay, I just want to ask you, is this a real statue or is my leg being pulled in several
directions?
Where is the picture?
Okay, where the directions it could be pulled is
Is the
Civilization is that real look at that picture?
You know honestly these days
It is difficult to judge
You know at a quick at a quick glance it can be difficult to go to make an assessment, but um
at a quick glance at a quick glance I would say I don't see anything wrong with this but
Um, if you're telling me that you're concerned about if it's air AI or not, maybe it's worth giving
I mean the thing is you don't know that because the thing is right you're right, okay, right?
There was a period of time before you know, it's probably there, but the thing is you can modify the metadata
In images you can modify it to say okay. Well this images from 2016
but i remember you can modify it i thought before ai was popular i mean i so i've seen this for
quite a few years now like this oh there's a roman where is this so i'll tell you about it let me
see so this is uh do you know where it is i mean did you take the picture right now so this says it
is you took the picture i didn't take the picture but it says it's a roman sculpture
And I'm looking through the comments right now.
It says something that I'm honest with you.
It says the possibility of the ancient Roman
Martian method of Gopalgarum
might have some more bearing than you think.
Martian M.M. and Roman numerals is 2000,
the same year which M and M became a household name.
Coincidence, you just said.
So there's no, like.
People saying oh, this is a statue of this and this and this they're just making jokes about mom spaghetti and stuff
I don't know if it's supposed to be Julius Caesar or what but I don't I think it's like people are playing our leg
Whatever you want to whatever you want to think so that's the that's just the statue of you know the M&M statue
There you go. I you know, I think that we're much better looking guys say I didn't make a cute couple actually
And if you ever came to the dark side, I mean the only reason it's a dark side is because that's like
You know there's a tree there
We can like get under the shade and stuff like that and have as much sex as we want no one will ever know
What do you think about that?
I think
This is a wonderful vision
But I would rather have this vision with a woman
And I mean not disrespect to you
What I mean
Like like for example like beta. I
Don't think I don't think this would be I don't think it would be the most fulfilling sexual encounter. I
Don't think I think it would probably be the most satisfying
But now fulfilling this is how these things go
Hey, I had sex with beta and everyone be like, oh my god. I mean, that's not my concern
What is would it be there? I'm sure I'm sure that it would be very
Satisfying, but it wouldn't be fulfilling. You know what I mean
I'd like what she looks like that's what she looks like she looked like you think you've ever seen in real life
Or does she look like an AI?
Generated image of her
It looks like what I like to see
I would not sell them.
Probably AI generated an image of her because I've seen her on camera and she doesn't look at anything.
No, I've seen like non AI generated real people in like in my face with their titties.
You know what I mean?
Say, if I had bigger titties would you like?
No disrespect.
Would you like me if I had titties?
Do I need to get a present?
I mean, I think you kind of look like O'Henio Derbez.
Number number one number one problem is that you like you let me know disrespect to you
I'm just saying you you look like a man
Number one. Okay, number one problem. You look like a man. Okay?
Yeah, okay, you've got this okay put on the wig all right. Let's go on
Now you'd be Patriot. Okay. Now now you have the wig on second part
Second part you have facial hair
But it's like a little bit of it. Oh, this is tickle your butthole a little bit when I go in there
Second part. Yeah, not only do you have facial hair?
But you also have the facial structure of a man
I mean like I like even if you did not have facial hair
I would look at you and I can determine you are a man and again, no offense to you like I'm just like
You mean the thing is also right even if I was not able to see your face I could kind of like
You can tell you know someone's demeanor right the way that someone behaves
Well, here's the thing psyche you're the moment that you're like oh oh sake get the fuck out of here
I'm gonna kick you out
I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I would never say that, I
Right, you behave all sensitive and all this and this and that
Give me yourself away. That's my point
Right, you know, no not necessarily I know a lot of women that are you know women I
Fucking put my dick in them in it feel like it feels like a woman
They don't act like they don't act all like retarded bitches, you know, no disrespect to nobody
What what what say clear clear dick in their booty hole and then now tell the difference
They usually like him or when I put it in there for Diana, but I want it in the air. I mean
Okay, but you're not my target audience you understand
I mean why you why do you want it? Why do you want to hurt my feelings? I'm not trying to hurt your feelings
I don't think I am
I don't think I am hurting your feelings
You are I think I have my doubts
Well, I might ask about you, but you know what, you're so cute, I like your haircut, I like your haircut, you're doing a line right now.
I appreciate your compliments.
I like your haircut, it's cute, it's fitting on you.
Because a lot of Mexican guys just do like the bowl haircut, like all around their head, have you ever seen that?
What is that haircut? I don't understand.
I appreciate your compliments, thank you.
Because you don't look like you had your haircut by a flow bee.
I don't know if you know what a flow bee is, but that's a lot of...
Mexican guys nowadays this I got my hair cut up by a float be yes
I did
But what is this look where the Mexican guys that they combed on their hair like in a circle?
It looks they look like they're from that movie with milk the Mel Gibson
What was that like where he like that Mexico that Mel Gibson movie where he'd like did like that
The Aztec people and they all had this this haircut. Have we been there guests? Okay, I'm gonna put the link down for you guys
I couldn't tell you. Oh, it's called apocalyptica apocalyptica or something. Do you ever see that?
No
Well, it's not Mexicans that were like Aztecs or whatever and they like maybe that was a crazy initiation rituals and they were like out
Shooting arrows and animals and then the Spanish came whatever
But they have this haircut and now I go on tiktok every missing guy has this haircut
It's basically like they take a flow bee they cut their hair
And then they like put in a bunch of gel and they just comb it in like a perfect circle around their head and it looks so bad
do you know anything about this i couldn't tell you i don't know nothing about it okay he doesn't
know because guys look at Siggins look at his his hair he's here okay we have another guest
say do you want to say hi to our guests that's up to you i didn't get this one to talk to you
he's a really cute hot guy one of my favorites on the show let's welcome to the show his name
Can you guess who it is?
Alexander McQueen McQueen, yes, exactly
Yo, let's be brown
Say you lose your five Mexican retarded less
You will mean to
You're retired, nigga. Shut the fuck up, pussy-ass-ing-o.
You're the one that's attacking town. You're jealous. You're a jealous loser.
You definitely pornbomb. All you do is sit in your stupid-
NYPD.
Pornbombing everybody.
Alex, all I'm gonna tell you...
You fake news, Mexican faggot.
Alex, I know people in NYPD that they will smack the shit out of you, nigga.
Tell you that right now.
I know people in the bureau, that would smack the shit out of you nigga, they would be like, what's up nigga, they would smack the shit out of you, and then they would be like, what's up nigga, do something nigga, do something, and you wouldn't do nothing about it man, all I've got to say, you want to trip on me nigga, you're tripping nigga, you're tripping fool.
All I got to say.
Oh fuck, you're Mexican, shut up!
I'm glad that you're enjoying hearing your own fucking voice.
You shouldn't have even been here, bro.
You fucking stupid faggot.
Enjoy hearing yourself talk,
fucking stupid idiot,
embarrassing yourself.
stupid ass motherfucker congratulations
you know these kinds of people they're too fucking pussy to put their name behind what they're doing
you know i mean oh i'm nypd i'm nypd let me see your badge number oh your nypd what's your
badge number what's your name what's your what is your name okay your mr nypd what's your name
You want a banana?
It's that simple.
You're just too fucking pussy, though.
You're the kind of fucking faggot.
You just wanted to say that you're a white pete,
but you're not really like that, nigga.
You trippin'.
You retire like a bitch, nigga.
Just you and psyche, right? That's how it is. Now you didn't make your way up.
You just retire like a little bitch. That's how it is.
And the spinal got shut down by you. That's who I know.
And all the losers, right? But I'll hold them constantly.
Keep, keep talking. Keep making yourself feel better, stupid ass.
And now you think like I'm moving away?
Keep making yourself feel better, stupid bitch.
You think I'm going away, asshole?
stupid ass bitch your ass was in the NYPD and you never made your way up you never made your way
up stupid ass bitch okay never made your way up and instead you come to these streams and you try to
brag oh i'm mr nypd i'm mr nypd stupid ass bitch negative please peace out
Airplane mode I felt it in my skin
Oh, it's a negative place because I'm telling this fucking faggot
So I was sitting like design ago
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we've learned
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you craved the chaos I fed
Cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna crush you
I could never rise above you
But I'm under him tonight
Don't call it rage, it's recollection
Not to be divine, but I love you
This sin was born from your reflection
Not to be celestial, but you made my claim perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from a stranger's lair
Just to prove that I still care, you'd fall apart
Cause you know it's true, no one sins the way I do
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna curse you, I could never
I was already broken
You can't forgive
What was never spoken
Every scar, a holy mark
Every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine, but I love you